shoepalace.com 2014-11-05

# Privacy Policy at Shoe Palace

At www.shoepalace.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document explains the manner, in which “Shoe Palace” collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the “www.shoepalace.com” website. This privacy policy applies to the “Shoe Palace” Site and all products and services offered by “Shoe palace”.

## Information Collection:

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers’ utilized and other similar information.

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## Information Use and Disclosure:

Shoe Palace website “www.shoepalace.com” may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

#### To improve customer service

Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

#### To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

#### To improve our Site

We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

#### To process payments

We may use the information Users provide about them when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

#### To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature

To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

#### To send periodic emails

We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

## Data Security:

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

## Updates To This Policy:

Shoe Palace has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using the Shoe Palace Site, www.shoepalace.com, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

**Shoe Palace Corporation** **Website: www.shoepalace.com** **Corporate Address:** 300 Enzo DriveSan Jose, CA 95138 **Phone:**  888.772.5223 Fax: 408.629.1200  **Email:** customerservice@shoepalace.com
